A Guide to the Wormley Family Papers, 1773-1991 (bulk 1880-1960)
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Supplemental Volumes, 1820-1991 (bulk 1860-1900 and 1978-1989)
  - Wormeley-Wormley ca. 1160-1991: The Father-To-Son Lineage of Stanton L. Wormley, Jr. Compiled by Stanton L. Wormley, Sr., Stanton L. Wormley, Jr., and Paul E. Sluby, Sr. in 1991. (Box 8)
  - Wormley Family Genealogy Volumes 009-073 (Compact discs) (Box 8)